superpoints.com 2010-02-09

# SuperPoints Network

**Westlake Products, Inc. Privacy Policy - August 2009**

Westlake Products, Inc. (the "Company") respects your privacy. In that regard, we have created this Privacy Policy to let you know what information we collect when you visit our “SuperPoints Network” of websites (the “Websites”) and use the associated services that are available if you become a member, why we collect it, and how it is used. By using a Website or creating a member account, you consent to the data practices prescribed in this Privacy Policy. The Company's Privacy Policy governs the privacy guidelines for the Websites. 

### What information does the Company collect?

"Personal Information" means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, first and last name, home or other physical address, credit card information, an email address, phone number, or other contact information, whether at work or at home. 

In a few areas on our Website(s), in providing services and through online customer support tools, we may ask you to provide Personal Information that will enable us to enhance your use of the Website(s) or for purposes such as facilitating correspondence with you, registering your entitlement to access certain special features of the Website(s), or to complete transactions. It is always your choice whether or not to provide that Personal Information. If you choose not to provide requested Personal Information, you may not be able to use certain features of the Website(s). 

For example, when you use the referral features of the Website(s) (the "Referral Program"), we may ask you to provide information such as your email address and your user and/or password information at another website or service. This will allow us to access your online address book, which includes your friends’ email addresses, so that we can send email invitations to them on your behalf. You will be able to choose who we send invitations to and we never store the login information you provided. When your friends receive an invitation you initiated, they will be given the opportunity to become Members, and make referrals to their friends also. If the people you invited to the service do not respond to the initial invitation request, we will attempt to send them additional invitations some time in the future. We do this because sometimes the initial attempts are not delivered to their inbox and so they never actually saw the initial invitations. We may use the data we collect in connection with these communications for the operation and ongoing maintenance of the Referral Program and the services we offer through the Website(s). You and your friends may opt-out of participation in the Referral Program at any time via opt-out links in all communications made to you and your friends through the Referral Program or by logging into your account and clicking on the "Settings" link at the top of the page and then clicking on the “Communication Settings” button and stating your request in the form provided. 

We may also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, which could include your IP address, cookie information, browser information, and the page you request. 

### How does the Company use Personal Information?

Except as described in this policy, the Personal Information you provide will be kept confidential and used to support your customer relationship with the Company. Among other things, we want to help you quickly find information on our Website(s) and alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new products and services from the Company. The Company may enhance or merge your information with data from third parties for purposes of marketing products or services to you. 

Personal Information that you enter into your public profile will be shared with other users. Your first and last name, your gender, marital status and birth date will be displayed on your public profile 

Periodically, we may send you information about our various products and services, or other products and services we feel may be of interest to you. These mailings may be sent electronically or in physical form. Only the Company (or agents or contractors working on behalf of the Company and under confidentiality agreements, or other Members) will send you these mailings. If you do not want to receive such mailings, simply tell us when you give us your Personal Information. Or, at any time you can easily opt-out of receiving further marketing from the Company by contacting us and requesting to have your name removed from our marketing lists. In addition, with respect to mailings sent via email, you may also click the "unsubscribe" link in the email to have your email address removed from our marketing list. All requests to unsubscribe will be handled in a prompt and efficient manner and in accordance with applicable law. Please also be advised that Members cannot unsubscribe from Administrative Messages while they are Members, so if you unsubscribe from Administrative Messages your Membership will be terminated. 

We track product usage data to improve the services we offer to our Users. We collect User traffic patterns throughout our Website(s). This information is collected to help improve website flow and usability. In addition, we track click-through information, including IP addresses, to our Website(s) from the reports and emails we sent to our customers. This is done to gauge the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns and to discourage fraudulent use. 

We may aggregate Users’ nonpersonal information and share this information with our partners, and/or sell this information. 

### Updating Your Personal Information

To update any of your personal information or to change any of your marketing preferences, you may update your personal information through the Website(s) by logging in and accessing the “Account” area. 

### Information Sharing and Disclosure to Third Parties

Agents or contractors of the Company may have access to your Personal Information for the purpose of performing services on behalf of the Company. All such agents or contractors who have access to your Personal Information are required to keep the information confidential and not use it for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for the Company or as otherwise required by law. In addition, information collected about you may be shared with other third parties as expressly stated on the page on which you provided such information. 

Except as set forth in this policy, the Company does not rent, sell or share Personal Information it collects about you to or with third parties. In addition to the sharing and use of your Personal Information as described in this policy, the Company or its agents or contractors may also disclose Personal Information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (1) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of the Company or its agents or contractors; or (3) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Company, its Website(s) or the public. If the Company should ever file for bankruptcy, merge with another company, or sell our assets, we may sell the information you provide to us via a Website to a third party or share your Personal Information with any company with whom we complete such transaction. 

### Security of Your Information

Any online payment transactions occurring on the Website(s) will be secured using industry standard encryption technology (e.g., Secure Sockets Layer). 

You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online. If you post Personal Information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. While we strive to protect your Personal Information, the Company does not ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. 

### Third-Party Sites

Please be aware that other websites that may be accessed through our Website(s) may collect personally identifiable information about you. This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of those third-party websites linked to our Website(s). 

### International Transfers

Personal Information collected via our Website(s) may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which the Company or its affiliates, subsidiaries, agents or contractors maintain facilities, and by using the Website(s), you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. 

### Children's Privacy

The Websites are not intended for or directed to persons under the age of 18. Any person who provides their information to the Company through the account login page for new customers or any other part of the Website(s) represents to the Company that he or she is 18 years of age or older. 

### Your Consent to this Privacy Policy

By using a Website, you agree to this Privacy Policy. This is our entire and exclusive Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. We may change this Privacy Policy by posting a new version of this Privacy Policy, and it is your responsibility to review this page periodically. When we do change the policy, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the Privacy Policy. Your continued use of a Website constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates. 

### Contacting the Company

For questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: 

Westlake Products, Inc.  
Attn: Privacy Policy  
7301 Ranch Road 620 N.  
Ste 155-182  
Austin, TX 78726 

You may also login to your account and click on the "help & support" link to contact us.
